before I begin this video I wanted to
say a huge thank you to those who have
supported my Etsy shop or my writing it
means the world and it really keeps this
channel going so thank you so much and I
hope you enjoy this cozy little q a
good morning everyone I hope you're
having a wonderful week so far apologies
in advance if you hear the rain and the
wind in the background it is somehow
managing to be sunny and rainy at the
same time it feels like a contradiction
to have sun rays and rain but it's
happening nonetheless this week it has
been a very rainy April Showers have
been very real and it has been so windy
that lawn chairs at times have been
flying past my window and so I decided
that it would not quite be appropriate
to be filming Outdoors when there are
flying projectiles through the air so I
thought I would do something a little
cozy a little cozy chat this week I know
that's not everyone's cup of tea so if
not I will see you next week with a lot
of Nature and wildflowers I hope hello
hi Hi how are you it's good how are you
doing I'm good I'm filming so you just
interrupted
come on just say hi I wasn't sure the
first question is I admire everything
you create but how do you keep your cat
away from it I think the answer to that
is I don't
um a lot of things get destroyed and um
I have quite a few regrets but mavi is
an extremely curious and involved very
social cat and so there's no really
keeping her away from whatever I'm doing
unless I lock her in a room which she
despises and holds against me for quite
a few days she has me well trained is
there anywhere in the world you would
like to travel I have not really thought
about that too much recently I actually
grew up traveling a lot my dad was in
the military most of you I'm sure know
that already but
um I grew up doing that and I I think
now I'm really enjoying kind of
staying put I know that is so odd I mean
who doesn't love to travel right
um I do of course enjoy traveling but
I've just done so much waiting in
airports waiting at restaurants waiting
at hotels waiting for cars throughout my
entire life that I'm just glad I don't
have to deal with all the logistics of
travel for a long time however if I
would go somewhere you know I would
really love to someday see the Lake
District in Britain I of course would
love to go back to Prince Edward Island
I'd love to see my brother he lives in
Australia now and I've never been to
Australia however if I really had to
choose where I'd want to travel I think
right now I would travel to Houston
Texas because that is where my sister
lives and I would love to see her right
now have you had any Supernatural
experiences I was surprised how often
this question popped up I did not know
so many of you had ghostly interests so
um I unfortunately cannot give you a
really good story do though uh share
your stories down below whether you um
believe in the Supernatural or not
um I do think they make wonderful
campfire stories and they are a lot of
fun to listen to and so um definitely
share below if you have any once when I
was really really young I was at a
shopping mall with my family and I got
separated from my family and I kind of
moved with the crowd kind of pushed with
the crowd into an elevator and it was an
extremely busy mall and it was a very
very scary experience and I was
extremely lost and quite far away from
my family and I remember a woman
appeared in the elevator the doors
opened and a woman appeared and she took
my hand and brought me to my family
who were quite a ways away and she just
led me there and uh my memory of her was
that she was wreathed in bright light I
would call her my guardian angel for
years after seeing her and it was a very
special experience so
maybe she was just a Good Samaritan and
I just imagined that she was glowing
from the inside out and Rays of light
were coming out of her but it is
interesting that she was a stranger and
my family has no memory of her
and she knew who my family was which is
interesting because if you see my sister
and my mother they have much darker skin
and darker hair than me so most people
don't think we're related and yet
somehow this woman knew we were so it
was uh it was interesting so you can
tell me what you make of that in the
comments section this is all in good fun
of course I don't want to be spooky
anyone
another question I got was several
requests for wardrobe tour but as I'm in
the midst of putting things in storage
from Winter I decided it wasn't quite
the right time to do that however I
thought I would share with you some of
my favorite spring dresses
I re-wear my dresses often you probably
will see some of my favorites again and
again in my videos
[Music]
I also have some favorite shoes that are
from the Dubliner brand I found they
last the longest and I really value
items that I can keep for possibly even
a decade or more which is the case with
these boots and I absolutely love them
and they're super comfortable and warm
so as I've been trying on all these
outfits to show you I've realized that
quite a few of them do not fit me
anymore especially the ones that were
already on the a little bit smaller side
when I got them I have gained about 10
pounds I think since this time last year
and it was intentional I realized that I
was just kind of snacking throughout the
day and not always stopping to enjoy a
wholesome nutritious meal so I really
wanted to make a point of doing that for
my health for my long-term health and
for my present energy and it has made me
feel so much better to take care of
myself better
however there are quite a few dresses
that I do need to find new homes for and
I'm realizing that this so
um yeah so there you go that's why I'm
not showing you as many as I thought I
was going to I will say however I do
wish I could share with you more
sustainable ethical brand options and
I'm going to do that that is a big goal
of mine a lot of the clothes I have are
from labels I wouldn't buy directly from
they are from thredup or they are you
know gifts or thrifted items and so I
really want to share with you some
ethically made options that I think are
beautiful so that is a goal that is
going to happen and I'm saving up my
money because
um there it's a lot more expensive you
know as it should be because everyone is
being paid really well and the clothing
is of a high quality so I want to do
that but it's going to take me a little
bit time to save up
okay back to the normal q a another
question was I'm trying to put my phone
away any tips
one tip that might be helpful to you if
you really want to cut down on your
screen time if you put it away for one
entire day if you're able to of course
you know we all often need to check it
for one thing or another but at least
trying to limit it as much as possible
you may be surprised to realize how much
you use it and how much time goes to
that and you might find that the
feelings arise might be quite
uncomfortable you might feel boredom or
maybe even anxious or just not knowing
what to do with yourself I think that
experience while might be slightly
unpleasant might help you understand
what type of relationship you want with
your screen time you know if you are so
reliant on it that it's really hard to
be away from it that might be a sign
that you want to discover other types of
hobbies and interests I would say
however it's definitely takes a little
bit of time there's a little bit of that
kind of withdrawal period I know in
college I used my phone a lot and then
it was um very strange to kind of wean
myself away from it and it took a while
but I did find that I am now able to
focus on projects such as reading or
painting or anything else
um with a lot more ease it takes a while
to build up that ability to refocus on
tasks that are not quite as entertaining
as what you might find on your phone I
don't know if that makes sense but I do
love to have soft music in the
background throughout the day sometimes
while I'm working on projects you know I
definitely think there's a balance it's
about using technology and social media
in a way that nurtures you so maybe just
developing your philosophy on that will
help you find a happy medium between
screen time and time doing other sorts
of hobbies and tasks will you make
another video similar to the winter
bunny tale you made before I do get this
question quite a bit I will leave the
link to the video they're talking about
below it is called I think a winter tale
I think I along with my sidekick actor
Mr Darcy created a fairy tale story and
filmed it together and it was a really
fun experience and it seemed like quite
a few of you really enjoyed that and I
would love to create another story like
that I just haven't quite found the
right story that I can abridge into a
short video I have a lot of stories but
they're all very long so I'm not quite
sure but I would love to make a new one
Carolyn Marie reads asks which three
books do you think everyone should read
at least once Carolyn is an amazing
booktuber if you don't know what a
booktuber is you can acquaint yourself
with the booktube community here on
YouTube and she does some really
wonderful wonderful videos I really
encourage you to check her out she is
just a lovely lovely human being and I
will link her Channel Down Below there
are two that come to mind immediate
lately and they are my two favorite
books which is Once Upon a river and the
snow child however I don't know if these
are books that I would recommend that
everyone read I just think they're some
of my favorite books if you are someone
who has experienced quite a bit of
trouble with worrying and anxiety and
stress I find the book fear to be a
really helpful book the book is written
by someone who is Buddhist but I think
that no matter what you believe or what
your um religious or spiritual beliefs
are I believe that at least most people
could gain something really powerful
from that book I found it very helpful
for me the boy the mole The Fox and the
horse is a really sweet very short kind
of Zen inspired book that I really love
it's absolutely adorable and I love that
it is poignant because of its Simplicity
The Hobbit is a fantastic book it's just
a really good book it's it's an
adventure story it is a classic
it is funny it is hopeful it is about
ordinary people doing extraordinary
things I highly recommend listening to
it as an audiobook I apologize Carolyn
because I definitely didn't answer the
question in the correct way I did not
name just three books I have a very hard
time narrowing things down I really did
love those books and I'm going to put
several more of them here other books
that I really love
because I know I'm going to come up with
a lot more another question I had was
what are my go-to hairstyles and my hair
care routine I will insert some images
of hairstyles I like to do that are
really basic I like to keep things
mostly simple however when it comes to
taking care of my hair all I do is put
some conditioner in a spray bottle and I
spray down my hair section by section in
the morning
foreign
so here are just a few of my basic
hairstyles I do every day they only take
a few minutes I will leave links to an
example on YouTube for the last one
because it's a bit tricky the other ones
just involve a simple English braid I
have these hair pins I use that are
designed for thick hair that I really
like they will not work on fine hair so
you were forewarned I inherited the
thick coarse hair of my Puerto Rican
ancestors so it's rather rough to the
touch it's not super soft but I can make
a lot of intricate hairstyles with it so
there are pros and cons
[Music]
thank you
how tall are you I am five foot nine
inches so yes to those of you that
comment saying that I look very very
tall it is because I am I am rather tall
whenever I wear boots though I'm easily
six feet tall so that um that was
something that I was not always
comfortable with growing up it is so
important to celebrate your body for so
many other things than how it looks gosh
I think that is one of the things I love
to do in meditation is to just take a
moment to think my arms my legs my head
my joints you know to be able to get me
more or less where I need to go I do try
to take time every day to really
appreciate what my body does for me life
that your body is giving you and your
mind as well to be grateful for that
Consciousness with for that gift I mean
I remember looking up once what the odds
were you had the opportunity to live a
life and those odds are very small it is
um it really puts things the perspective
of what a gift it is to be here right
now what a gift to be here with you what
do you eat I um get this question so
often and it's very very boring that is
why I haven't made a video specifically
on it you know I don't think I could
contribute of anything of worth I eat a
whole lot of pasta and rice and
chickpeas and potatoes and beans and
that's about it
I feel the best when I mostly
plant-based and I do love the
reducitarianism concept the sake of the
environment you know I try to not go
overboard on animal products and kind of
limit those while um just yes still
keeping things simple what are some of
your favorite movies I cannot think of
any right now for some strange reason so
I'm just gonna put photos of all of them
here because I know they're going to
come to my mind the moment I stop
filming but yes I do have quite a few
favorites why are you so happy I thought
this was a funny uh question because
um I just wanted to use it as a
opportunity to remind anyone watching I
do have the choice to be able to edit
these videos and if I'm having a
difficult day or if I am facing a
challenge in some way I do have the
opportunity to face that challenge
um away from the camera so I see these
videos as a way to tell stories to focus
on beautiful things and enhance the
beauty of this Valley and daily life
my life itself is extremely normal I
have good days I have bad days I am not
always happy and I do like to share a
little bit about that even though
visually I like to focus on beautiful
things mostly nature how is married life
going it has been lovely but it has been
a huge transition I wish that we opened
the conversation a little more of how
difficult it can be to move into a new
house to transition your entire life to
share a space with someone it um can be
such a big change and such a big
Challenge and sometimes as well not all
of it is smooth and perfect and I think
it is good to acknowledge that it has
been wonderful full of amazing moments
challenges stressful days and the
adventure of figuring out life together
and I'm so grateful for that what book
are you currently reading I'm actually
reading the wild Tales by Jackie Morris
and they are absolutely
delightful they're written like old
style fairy tales and both stories I'm
almost at the end of the second one so
far both stories have just been so
enchanting and I couldn't recommend it
enough so if I didn't get to your
question I do apologize I had to pick
and choose
um but if you are interested in past q
and A's where I may have answered your
question I'll list them down below I
don't plan to do another q a for quite a
while this is definitely due to the
weather not permitting me to be outside
and so
um I hope you enjoyed this and I hope
you have a wonderful wonderful week and
I will see you very very soon goodbye
thank you
[Music]